icongalore.com 2006-12-30

# Privacy policy

At Icongalore.com we respect your privacy and are committed towards protecting it by taking all measures possible. Kindly go through the following to find out how we treat personal information collected from our visitors and customers. 

**Collection of personal information**

Icongalore.com will not collect personal information without your consent. You can browse our website without revealing any personal information. However we do need some level of personal identifiable information to provide you our services. This includes icon purchasing and support. 

**Using Personal Information**

All personal information collected will be stored securely using network firewalls and access control procedures removing chances of any unauthorized access. Your information will be treated with utmost confidentiality and will be used solely by Icongalore.com for the purpose of business communication like providing support and service delivery only. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Your personal information is safe with us. Icongalore.com will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to third parties under any circumstances. 

**Security**

Icongalore.com makes use of the best practices to ensure that your online transactions are safe and your personal credit information is stored securely. However Icongalore.com will not be held responsible for any breach of security. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Icongalore.com reserves the right to make changes to this policy at its sole discretion. Any changes made in this manner will be posted on this page. Kindly visit this page periodically to check for changes.
